How did one person transform the global economy
Make it possible for us to eat fresh oranges in December
American T-shirts from Cambodia
My iPhone
Made in China
And what can the story of an outsider
Tell us about spring innovation
In the 1930s a young truck
Malcolm X
Pulled up to a ship
Deliver loader
Who's the day before
McLane have been driving all night
Got an early morning
Movie25
Who discovered it would take 9 hours brought the trucks in front of him
We unloaded and get their card was stuffed into the wind shifts
Longshoreman loading there was no expert in votes he was a trucker
But this was crazy
Ask for me
When adjusting trailer on the back of my truck and put it on board the ship
Rather than unloading and reloading everything
All the shippers knew that the only way to get more productive in moving cargo across oceans was the bill passed
Ships in the field every nook and cranny
McLean thought there must be a better way
What avails it once again
The guillotine
Listen to build faster boats
Ways to build faster dogs until complete 20 more years to convince everyone else
Givenchy had to buy his own boat
Invent a whole new system of cranes and come up with devices for logging shipping
When he was done now instead of taking the world's first container ship requires only 8 hours
Immigrant shipping cost
Remove $6 a tonne to just $0.16
Not going to transform not only the shipping industry but today the entire global economy
In the lesson here is that Outsiders often see Solutions the inside of the so-called experts
Pretty sure that we can all treat ourselves to
We can all see the big dumb idea that everyone else misses the secret
It's a listen to unexpected sources of information
Like an unknown truck
Entertain ourselves to question
What everyone else already knows this trip