You're only half right
You can see whole Nations
How to blanch it was just a few like we had never had before and I think my words of that time we review
Beautiful view
Which it certainly was
I want to cross the Atlantic going into the dark side
Then when I was coming out on the light side of the Earth again with the first rays of the sun coming
Coming through the Earth's atmosphere and to the spacecraft
The glass out the window it look like
Look like a summer evening out in the meadow some place where there are a few fireflies but there were millions of
As far as I could see
Wallflower of them coming but another graveyard really determined later on was it
Moisture particles
From the heat exchanger was a little drip of water comes out that then diffused into
Much smaller particles all over it
You're one of the few people who has been portrayed
During his lifetime in film
How do you think Ed Harris
Never met and he rose to this day
That way
People think we had something to do with it movie The Right Stuff and we didn't
Had no connection with them at all
When Hollywood got hold of that film is a sort of
Need free Fantasy 4
All is well stations
People that very often what's the most memorable
Event your life and I'll expect those space
Light of course and that is a big one
But I don't think anything ever surpasses what you doing come back
Those are some vivid things that are impressed on your memory
And I'm sure every veteran has been in combat would agree with that there's nothing compares to that
31 of my check out missions when I was flying waiting on there yet
Squadron Co we were down low and he got hit by any aircraft fire
Control airplane had to get out
It went down on the ground and
Scrub
Brush area and I saw the parachute being pulled in after he went down there and this is way up a couple of them
Mother behind the line
I calculated the amount of fuel I would need
To get back to altitude again enough to
Flying back over our own lines
Because I really thought we were just within minutes of ever getting him out of there
But I was down low and kept circling and circling and circling in the chopper never did get there in time so
When I get my minimum fuel enough to get me back to 40000 feet
Flamed out up there and glided back over our lines will
A good Tailwind at altitude that day and so I got back over our base
What would have happened was his little Danny
Blowing up and make a big
Sizzling noise
Insulating people in the soldier knew where to come
They were they got him and wash him off and leave
Later on he came out as a PW in the end of what was called Big switch on the prisoner exchange at the end of that
Time.
And I was able to be up there
Berated me and either way you love me forever to try to get you he said everytime you come around up there
Yeah they would throw me in a ditch and sit on me or step on me
Stand on me
And it really hurt my shoulder cuz he's already been shot
You only wanted me to do is just go away and go home
Guitar Center Glen
Let me ask you something is there anybody watching and you would like to take out the
In space with you and just
Leave there
Remind me to come up and help us understand if they want to come up here they wouldn't provide the money to bring me back so I'm glad
Are the reason I was up there as a matter of fact on the second flight wasn't just a final assignment
I had noted in some of the NASA
Material
That there were some 52 changes in the human body that occur in space
And over period of time
The Earth here the human body changes as you get older
There about 8 or 10 of those things like
The body's immune system you you get less resistant to disease infection of the error period of time the same thing
To the elderly right here on Earth
It might make it possible for the younger people to stay up in flight
Much longer without harmful effect that might even
Give us some clues of how we take away the frailties of old age right here on Earth
And then I volunteered for the flight and
Was told that I have to pass the same physical as everybody else oh and I was able to do that so
I felt the great Fortune to be up there with
4 days up there that I had that 21 different parameters were being recorded in and blood samples each day that I was
Was on that routine also
I understand you had a nickname
Don't know what that was
Well he told me that you called him Count Dracula
Scott became Dracula the movie as far as I was concerned we got the blood and that was all
That was the objective
That you grew up in a pretty small town in Ohio you grew up in New Concord
That's where you met and your wife could you just talk about
The experience of growing up in
Small town in America and what that did
For you
I think that there couldn't be a better place to grow up
Children watch for free
To do what they want to do and for more kids groups and go camping in
Swimming in the in the creek down the pull of the town
Who's the depth of the Great Depression
People would come up to our home from Old Route 40 the National Road
And knock on the front door and ask mother if she could spare him something to eat
A mother would always making a plate of food and I sit on the back steps needed
We planted a huge Garden
Another candle out of stuff in the end that became something it wasn't that we share with other people in town
I'm sure that those experiences in life everyday
The Concorde video
Affected my life
If you don't mind my asking how would you like to be remembered
I'm not interested in sitting looking back at legacies all the time I told someone too short time ago as far as the Legacy goes
I'll leave it up to what other people
Dean was important